If you are reading this that means that you can successfully reach my work though Github, that is a good start. The folders contain all the required files. The recreation of the files are also possible but first you need to set up the proper folder structure and copy the information there. I add a code here that you can copy to terminal to set up the folder structure.


1. Create a folder for my work and set it as wd:
cd ".../Benedek Assingment"

2. Create the folders: 
mkdir Stata
mkdir Python

cd "Stata"
mkdir data
mkdir data/raw

cd ..

cd "Python"
mkdir data
mkdir data/raw
mkdir data/clean
mkdir Python_output

3. Now copy the files into the folders

Place the .do files and the Python script in their respective folders (Stata and Python).
The file airbnb_london_listing.csv should be placed in the data/raw subfolder of both the Python and Stata directories.

4. Now if you run the codes the outputs and the clean data will be generated. 
In case of Stata only the data_analysis do file needed to be run as it uses de cleaning do as well. 

